Guide to the Michelangelo Signorile Papers ca. 1985-2000 MSS.131
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Research
  - Subseries B: General
    - Religious Right: Catholic church, evangelism, others, undated (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Safe Sex: Australian campaign, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Safe Sex: article and essay, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Safe Sex & Drugs:Sex Panic!, others, undated (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Safe Sex & Drugs: HIV Prevention conference, magazines, articles, undated (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Sex Panic!, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Sex Panic!: Flyer alleging sex crackdown, undated (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Trophy Boys: New York article, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Outweek: 4 "Absolutely Queer" celebrity(Flat) outing posters, undated (Box 13, Folder 123)
- Series III: Manuscripts
  Drafts of various articles and books, organized by approximate
  - Outweek, Malcolm Forbes story draft, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Advocate, "Absolutely Queer" columndrafts (2), 1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Queer in America: original proposal, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Queer in America: Advocate excerpt, draftswith edit notes (2), 1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Queer in America: Preface, Introduction—legal & copy-edit drafts, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Queer in America: Preface, Contents, Intro-duction—proof copy & draft, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Queer in America: 2 drafts with editsChapter 1—Lights, Cameras, ACT UP Chapter 2—A Queer's Own Story, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Queer in America: 2 drafts with edits Chapter 3—Hype Anxiety Chapter 4—Out of the Closets and Into the Streets Chapter 5—Outing, Part I, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Queer in America: 2 drafts with edits Chapter 6—Operation Out-the-Pentagon Chapter 7—Inning the Outing, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Queer in America: 2 drafts with editsChapter 8—Outing, Part II Chapter 9—All the Presidents' Queers, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Queer in America: 2 drafts with edits Chapter 10—The Crucifixion of Zelda Gilroy Chapter 11—From McCarthy to Medved Chapter 12—Smashing the Celluloid Closet, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Queer in America: 2 drafts with editsChapter 13—Outing, Part III Chapter 14—Resurrection of Sheila Kuehl, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Queer in America: 2 drafts with editsChapter 15—The Oregon Nightmare Chapter 16—The Silicon Solution, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Queer in America: "Queer Manifesto" draft, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Queer in America: Preface to British edition,draft, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Queer in America: Afterword to paperbackedition, multiple drafts with edits, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Inside the Christian Closet: 2 drafts with edits, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Outing Yourself: original proposal, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Out: column drafts (3), undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Out: Interview Transcript, MS interviewsUrvashi Vaid & Rich Tafel, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Out: "Bareback & Reckless" draft, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Life Outside: Acknowledgements, Introductiondraft with edits, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Life Outside: draft with editsChapter 3—Evangelical Church of the Circuit, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Life Outside: draft with editsChapter 4—Happiness in a Vial, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Series IV: Published Work
  - Subseries A: Articles
    Work published in magazines and newspapers by date, including an early portfolio and complete magazine issues
    - Pre-ACT UP Writing: Portfolio—Nightlife, Daily News Record, others, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Pre-ACT UP Writing: Daily News, Daily News Record, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Pre-ACT UP Writing: The Face, 2 issues, Dec 1997, Jan 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Pre-ACT UP Writing: People, The Face (3), 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Articles: NY Times, NY Post, NY Observer, Outweek, others, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Outweek: Malcolm Forbes outing issue, Mar 1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Outweek: New Clone/ Old Clone issue, Nov 1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Outweek: 2 issues, Apr 1991, May 1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Village Voice: MS Letter responding to decisionnot to publish Pete Williams story, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Advocate: Pete Williams outing issue, Aug 1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Advocate: "Absolutely Queer" columns, 2issues & loose, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Advocate: Columns & Articles, 5 issues, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - USA Today: Op-ed on outing, Mar 1992 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Advocate: "Out at the New York Times", 2 issues, May 1992 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Advocate: "Absolutely Queer" column, Jun 1992 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - New York Times: Op-ed on Oregon, Sep 1992 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Village Voice: 2 MS letters, 1992, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Advocate: Columns & Articles, 5 issues, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Out: "Signorile in America" columns, 3 issues, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Out: "Signorile in America" columns, 3 issues, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Out: "Signorile in America" columns, 3 issues, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Out: "Signorile in America" columns, 3 issues, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Out: "Signorile in America (Italy)" columns,3 issues, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Advocate: MS Letter on sex clubs, Oct 1997 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Out: "Signorile in America (Italy)" columns,3 issues, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Out: "Signorile in America" columns, 2 issues, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Subseries B: Books
    Published books consisting primarily of various paperback editions of Queer in America
    - Queer in America: Bound Galley, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Queer in America: Bound Galley, with notefrom editor inserted, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Queer in America: British paperback edition, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Queer in America: American paperback edition, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - The Night Larry Kramer Kissed Me, by DavidDrake, foreword by MS, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Queer in America: Japanese paperback edition, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Series V: Publicity & Marketing
  Various media coverage comprising publisher marketing, interviews, profiles, book reviews, other, by approx. date
  - Press Trip to Carnaval in Rio, Details article by Stephen Saban, May 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Gay Rights Activism, 1988-1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous: Profile, Interview, others, 1988-1992 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Outweek: Malcolm Forbes Outing,USA Today mention, Mar 1990 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Outweek: Profile of MS in Exposure mag, Sep 1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous: profile & quote, 1990, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Outweek: Forbes, Williams, other, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Outing: coverage of outing debate, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Outweek: 2 articles on fall of magazine, Jun 1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Pete Williams Outing, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Pete Williams Outing; Miscellaneous, 1991, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Pete Williams Outing, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Advocate: Voice ad announcing MS column, Nov 1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Outing; Queer in America: speeches, profile, others, 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Advocate: Lavender Enlightenment at the NY Times, coverage on article, Apr 1992 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Geraldo appearance: coverage, Apr 1992 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Newsweek, "Cultural Elite 100": NYT ad, Sep 1992 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Newsweek, "Cultural Elite 100": issue, Oct 1992 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous: MS speech; Sandra Bernhard, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Interviews, other, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Gay Journalists: 3 articles, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Interviews (2), 1992, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Interview: transcript from British documentary, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Speaking Engagements; Festivals: correspondence, conference info, other, 1993-1998 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Queer in America: Random House marketing,literature, correspondence, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Queer in America: reviews, excerpts, pre-publicity, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Queer in America: reviews, interviews, other, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Queer in America: reviews, interviews, other, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Queer in America: British trade write-up, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Queer in America: ads, bestseller listing, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Queer in America: interview, Jun 1993 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Queer in America: reviews, interviews, other, 1991, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Queer in America: reviews, appearances, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Queer in America: book listing, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Queer in America: coverage on outing ofunnamed 'Legislator', undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Queer in America: Queer Nation releaseouting unnamed 'Legislator', Jul 1993 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Queer in America: Anchor Books authorquestionnaire, undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Queer in America: Anchor Books catalogue, Sep 1994 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Key West International Gay Arts Festival: invite, festival info, Jun 1994 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Out: Press release announcing MS hiring, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Out: "Unsafe Like Me" coverage, relatedarticles, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Outing Yourself: speech, interview, other, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Outing Yourself: reviews, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Outing Yourself: interviews, reviews,appearances, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Outing Yourself: Random House memowith review, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous: Interviews, quote, other, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous: Out coverage, quotes, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Life Outside: HarperCollins catalogue, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Life Outside: HarperCollins marketing, adsfor author appearances, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Life Outside: Promotional postcard, invite, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Life Outside: Reviews, listings, interview, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Life Outside: Review, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Life Outside: Reviews, coverage, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Life Outside: Reviews, interviews, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Life Outside: Appearances, coverage, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Life Outside: #1 Book listing, Oct 1997 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Life Outside: #1 Book listing, Aug 1998 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Life Outside: NY Public Library awardnomination, correspondence, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Miscellaneous: reviews, quotes, appearances, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Genre magazine: "100 Men We Love of theCentury", Jan 2000 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Series VI: Legal
  Access to this series is restricted.
  - Queer in America Legal Review: largedocument case containing source info used during extensive Random House legal review, undated (Box 10, Folder —)
  - Advocate, Pete Williams story: Letter accepting story for publication; copy of confidential source notes required by editor prior to publishing, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Queer in America Legal Review: portion of Random House review with queries on book's claims & MS responses to queries, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Queer in America: sample release contract, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Life Outside: interview release contract, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Series VII: Media
  All media materials of the collection including videos of TV programs and documentaries & audio tapes of reporter interviews
  Audiovisual and born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Videocassette: Testing the Limits Collective PBS documentary on ACT UP & AIDS, VHS Sony T-120, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Videocassette: "Larry King Live," MS, Randy Shilts, Robert Bauman on outing, VHS Scotch T-120, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Videocassette: "Arsenio Hall," Harvey Fierstein discusses outing, MS mentioned, VHS Ampex T-120, Apr 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Videocassette: San Francisco TV coverage of Pete Williams outing, VHS Sony T-30, Aug 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Videocassette: PBS Freedom Foundation, MS interview on outing, VHS 3M T-30, 28:46 mins., Jan 1996 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Videocassette: "Leeza," MS interview on coming out, Apr 1996 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Audiocassette: Outweek, Malcolm Forbes story, telephone interviews, Fuji DR-I 90, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Audiocassettes (2): NLGJA conference, MS & Randy Shilts speeches, Sep 1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Audio microcassette: Interview with ACT UP Portland (OR) leaders on Mark Hatfield, TDK MC-60, Jan 1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Audio microcassette: Advocate: interview with Ron Reagan, Jr., Sony MC-60, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Audio microcassette: Advocate, "Out at the NY Times," interview with reporter Jeff Schmaltz, TDK MC-60, Jan 1992 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Audio microcassette: Queer in America: interview with actor Michael Kearns, Memorex MC-60, Mar 1992 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Audio microcassette: Queer in America, interview with Mattachine Society founder Frank Kameny, Sony MC-30, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Audio microcassette: 2 Interviews—NGLTF's Urvashi Vaid (Side A), Marvin Leibman (side B), Sony MC-60, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Audio microcassettes (2): Queer in America, interview with David Burns, hustler, on Geffen & Diller, Sony MC-60, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Audio microcassette: Queer in America, interview with Jonathan Rotenberg, Silicon Valley CEO, Panasonic MC-60, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Audio microcassette: Queer in America, interview with Paul Barressi, porn star on John Travolta, Memorex MC-60, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Audio microcassette: Queer in America, interviews with Dick Sargent & gay rights pioneer Morris Knight, Sony MC-60, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Audiocassette: Queer in America, MS interviewed by David Gold on Dallas radio, Sony 60, May 1993 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Audiocassette: Queer in America, interview of MS on San Francisco radio, Jun 1993 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Audio microcassettes (7): Out, Hawaii gay marriage story, interviews, Sony/Panasonic MC-60, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Audio microcassette: Out, interview with Urvashi Vaid & Rich Tafel, TDK MC-60, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Audio microcassettes (5): Out, Republican convention, interviews & events, Sony/ Memorex MC-60, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Audio microcassette: Out, Miami murder story, interviews, Maxell MC-60, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Audio microcassette: Out, interview with Leslie Feinberg, transgender activist, TDK MC-60, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Audio microcassette: Out, interview with Ricki Ann Wilchins, transgender activist, TDK MC-60, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Audio microcassettes (5): Out, Italy murders, various interviews, Sony/TDK MC-60, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Audio microcassette: Life Outside: interview with Marvin Leibman, TDK MC-60, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Audio microcassette: Republican convention, interviews, TDK MC-60, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Computer Disks (3): Queer in America, research articles, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)